[Music]
fwd recover first provides excellent
coverage for critical illnesses it is an
affordable critical illness plan with
rich features and benefits
[Music]
my clients understood the need for a
critical illness plan like fwd recovers
as a way to secure income replacement in
the event of an unfortunate critical
illness diagnosis and how the lump sum
payout can support them financially
there was an exceptional case where fwd
provided one of my clients coverage for
a pre-existing medical condition
my client submitted her medical reports
for pre-underwriting and fwd responded
quickly to accept her own standard terms
she was so happy to get her coverage
from fwd as the condition was excluded
by another insurer
[Music]
the pandemic has told us that it is
imperative to have robust medical and
investment plans today you discovered 19
tomorrow it could be something else we
cannot control life's uncertainties but
we can definitely plan for it to
substantiate cancer stroke or heart
attack may or may not happen but in the
event it happens
fwd recovers can provide that much
needed financial cushioning
[Music]